So Industrial will be learning about React.
Its hooks, how two minutes deep with hooks will be getting our data from API, as well as we'll learn
how to manage state.
And at the end of the tutorial, we'll be deploying it up on the Heroku server.
So let's take a tour around that app.
So basically, it's a tool to step in this project.
People can be in different places with their details as well as their pricing, and if they are not
invested in that particular place, they can remove that from their UI.
And if we will get a new set of leaders, so this is all about the ad that we're making, though it
may not seem as very much, but believe me, you'll be learning quite helpful concepts and react that
will be helping you in the future applications.