So now that we have added every piece of code that our app needs, it's now time to take a look at it.
So if Kara received, there is nothing.
They are just placeholders.
So this does means that we are not getting any sort of data.
We are not displaying it.
So let's fix this.
So now let's first confirm whether we are getting the data from our API and as you are storing it in
our tools object.
So we can't allow the value of tools so that we can confirm that without getting our data or not.
So let's just console.log the value of tools and place to us in an object in the codebases.
So will this console.log and inside Libya says they'll write those stories to the state object, which
is holding an object of travelling data?
No, if we just open up our console, we can control shift I.
We will be seeing an error which actually fixing shortly as well as some objects inside it.
And these objects holds the value of what we are going to output and ultimately.
We see that there's a dos object with five values in it.
It is an area of objects with zero one, two, three, four and five that name I.D. indicates.
So now let's go back to it up and make certain changes that are incremental.
Be done.
So first of all, be getting rid of all this data because this is not what we are getting from our API.
If we again open up our console.
We'll see.
There's a different set of data with different developers that we're getting in here.
So the first set of data that we are receiving from our API is the 80 property and the name.
And we just open it may we're getting information name, as well as the price of the place that we're
going to go.
So let's go back and change all these values to 80 place price and other.
Values and image is going to be the photo of the place that we are going to go.
We have got the info, we have got the name and the price.
Information is the information of that particular place will be the caller wants to know.
The name and price.
OK.
No, replacing all the values for the source element will be just giving you the source value of image
because that's the image and really the art of name.
And in the Atualmente will again replace the word title with name.
And with the sub, this is basically the inflow of other of the places, so we'll just replace it with
an info.
And now, rather than the static data, will be to dynamically with price.
OK, let's just hit save and view it up again.
But before we do that, let's go to our tools object, and there was one error that we were seeing their
key value pair.
So we'll assign us to a kill I.D..
We'll give it a try because each value of each element of a map should have a specific key that is not
applicable.
So we'll go to Italy and Italy specific to a particular object, 2.8 to.
And it's safe, and let's go back now, I heard that up, and we'll see.
OK, let's clear our console first.
And then again, refresh our up.
Will they not?
Single area of objects.
So now we're getting our data and we are displaying it on our screen, so as you can see, there's different
faces, but there's a dollar sign missing, so that's just a dollar sign in our tour component in another
price.
We let a dollar sign.
Because how is the use of us to know whether it's a dollar pound euro?
OK, now we have it all the time and everything in this place, but still they're not interested.
Burton isn't working, right, so what we'll do is add.
Functionality to not interested in button.
So if we go to our dashboard, we'll create a function with Konst.
Let's name it, remove a tool and give it the.
Property ID.
Argument at the end.
Now let's create another object.
Call it going to new doors.
This is going to be the ability to after one particular tool has been deleted and we will be filtering
the tools in this.
So it goes further than a gain of function call back.
I will give it a tool and which should be equal to.
If 2.80 told Ali is not equal to the idea that we have received, then we are supposed to return the
value.
So that is going to match, we have to exterminate that value.
It is no longer in the government to be shown on up and we were setting new to so what sector is going?
It does.
It is going to have data to it.
So the object that we had actually deleted won't be showing on again and again.
We are to pass this as an as a prop to our other components to remove dirt and give it a value of remove
dirt.
OK, then again, let's move to a truce component, because that's that's the next level.
And he'll be receiving along with the tools they remove to the object.
Remove those.
And again, to pass it along to a tour component that removed those equals to remove those.
And he'd say then we have to go to our to object and we'll be receiving removed it from a previous component
that is and again, we'll create a button and respond click we'll call this function and click Let's
give it the arrow function and call to remove to.
OK, so we have a remote, we're over here and we'll get the I.D. that of the particular object.
And let's just hit save and view up.
To leave Europe again.
And click not invested, we will see an error.
So why is this error coming up?
Let's just read it.
It's removed already and the rest is removed or is not a function.
Let's just refresh it again.
OK, so probably it has some sort of typo in it.
So now let's head back to Iraq component, so we see removed doors.
It is fine over here.
OK, so they're supposed to be told not to.
So this was a disorder, Typekit admitted.
So let's just remove the word is from a function.
And again had to and it is going to be towed.
Let's confirm it again.
It has to be stored, not doors.
OK, now if we just click not infested VXR components getting disbanded from our UI.
OK, so it's functioning now.
So we have is fully implemented rendering of the components as well as we are removing them.
Now it's time to add loading as well as some other functionalities to adapt.
So really focusing on it now?