So now we'll be adding another component to add up, and this is going to be a loading campaign that
is going to show up every time an app is being loaded.
So for that purpose, inside tools for level making another company known as loading stodgy ASX.
And once we made, let's just move into that world of.
Loading, it's not Jesus.
And then as we move into this folder, the first step is to import and react, react from the atmosphere.
So just import, react from react.
And now we'll be creating a functional component concert.
Concert loading.
That is an out of function.
And that's just exported.
Otherwise it would be of no use to us export default and loadings.
And.
They put up a written statement in a functional component.
So it just return.
Now it is going to have a dearth of class name loading.
And.
No, it has to have a closing or closing tax, so let's just close it.
There.
It into now will have an edge forward heading, which is going to have which is going to have the words
loading and no, let's just make it one because it would be way too small.
And let's move to our dashboard and inside our dashboard.
Be making another bizarre state, and this is going to be a learning piece of state and city learning
as a setup function.
And initially, we want that loading to be true.
So just use state and the default value of the loading is going to be true and we'll be putting up if
statement after this.
So we have a loading as well as sector loading and default status too.
So just beneath our use effect and just above in a written statement, just if learning is true, then
we want it to return.
These are fragment.
Inside, this will be passing and importing allerdings component armados folder, so learning.
And let's close it.
It must have been at all important.
Yeah, it is now in another statement.
And this is going to state that if loading the land, no, it should be left to his department.
Let's just move this if those dirt land, you can equal to zero.
If those Deutschland Tripoli votes to zero.
Then what we want, what we want is that we will just put up a written statement and inside this and
incident will have a man inside this man will put up a different last name, Typekit.
And what really is going to hold it is going to hold an edge to that of a reef not always available.
And after this is true, dad will make up a button element.
Of class name between.
Median and on click whenever this button is collectively what we want function to refresh our up.
So give it an arrow function, and we'll be calling.
Get.
We'll be calling our function.
Which is get.
Those.
So what this basically is going to do that if it does, if it happens that we are getting no amount
of data from our API, so what we are going to do is it's going to refresh so that we can actually press
that data again.
So then just head to.
OK, now there's a bit of more tweaking that we need to do.
Just beneath our response or just resetting our loading equals too fast because if an app is going to
reach our response to our Jason, that means if I 179, that means we have successfully downloaded the
data and now the sideloading is supposed to return.
False.
So now we have said, we have said, noting, first of all.
Now it's time to save it up, and everything is working fine.
It has been completed successfully.
Now let's just view it up, so to check that whether everything's going fine or not.
So let's move into a browser.
So in our browser, if we see that.
Okay, let's just hit refresh to get the piece to see whether it's functioning or not.
Okay.
Everybody's been murdered.
Hit refresh.
You will see loading.
OK, we are seeing a loading, but we do not want to be in the extreme that extreme left.
We want to be in the center of the page and it is on extreme left.
So let's just move into a indexer ceasefire and make certain changes were there.
So now they wait.
So now we'll be targeting.
Loading screen.
So there's one left, no, just not loading.
And it should be on centre text, eventually a centre and.
Since he had got the chance, let the.
Serious property to a title as well as.
So deselected was indeed an amazing burden should be around for him.
OK, now let's just hit refresh again.
OK, now it's in the center.
So yes, it's really created a loading screen.
Now let's move forward.
Now, if we look at another piece of code, the what was left.
This is going to show up on their own live episode.
Our zero talent, but I can say that I just of blew of this device refresh button.
It looks kind of nasty.
So to fix this, let's move into our index assess, fail and target.
It's class that is button with.
Give it the background of excel to and five.
And a display of line block.
And after this will give it a.
Tithing, 0.2 firearm and 0.5 and a radius of 0.5.
Let's hit save and you are up.
So we can see that it is looking different from before, but again, we'll put up some more gold into
our rotate notices so that we can refactor it a bit more.
So will your tax transformation of capitalism to catalyze it all the world?
And how do you give it a color up hashtag Tribulus?
Then that's an invite, but a different shade.
And other than this value, add a little spacing of 0.1.
No, it's seven review crap.
So our text has definitely changed, as well as the colour of our text.
Now, because our pointer?
And, OK, now if you're holding with it, we can see your point.
And then a margin of to and a font size of 1.2.
I just hit save and let you add Europe.
So this is the button that we were looking for.
It is going to refrigerator, but since I have turned off my network, it is not loading any sort of
data.
No.