So now that our app is completely ready, it's time for deployment.
So where are we going to deploy our app?
But app on the head?
Ocasek, head of the cloud platform, as a service supporting several programming languages.
So we are going to deploy it app on this server.
And there is a catch to it will have to actually add up a battery pack.
So let's just move into how to go.
It's totally free app, so all you need to do is actually just log in with it and it will give you your
dashboard as you can see mine.
So once you reach on a dashboard, just click on New to create a new app and create a new app.
After that, you'll have to enter the name of the app.
So let's limit driver's.
So let's name it travels, so if we see this name is not available travel, so let's just name it travel
list.
App.
So our travel list app is name is available, so let's just create our app and prior to trading windows,
choose the region nearest to you.
For me, it's here, maybe for you, with my United States.
And if it's your idea and just do it and click on create new app.
So now here is that dashboard.
So we're going to deploy our app, so there are three ways in which they actually deploy our app to
adequacy or through up through containing registry that is again, Erghezi.
So they'll be using the GitHub option.
So just move to a GitHub.
Now we need to have our code inside our GitHub repository.
The first thing that will do is move into our data repository and let's just go to our guitar.
And we're pushing hard core into this, so for that purpose, let's create a new new repository.
And once you do this.
OK, so the name of my repository is going to be travels.
It can be anything.
There is no restriction on the name, you can actually name it anything.
So I'm just naming it travels and it is available, then it is going to a public repository and then
just create a repository.
No one's about the trees created, and I will be pushing out code into this, so if you haven't done
this before, you just follow along with me.
Just get initialized at app.
So just move into your source code and open a terminal.
Not just getting attacked.
We just get in it.
And then hit enter.
So a repository has been initialized.
Now let's move back and see what the next command is, he won't be adding Read me because it is already
available in our app and will make it the first commit.
So just copy this, come on and again, paste it in our.
Mean.
And then just hit enter.
OK, so we have to just first added, get ad space and a period.
So again, it is not OK, you know, the next command is.
Get real adding remote building, the address on which it has to be pushed.
So we just moved back.
Phil Gordon paste the following command.
OK, you have ordered Origin to adapt.
Now we're really pushing code to get.
So then again, pasted and hit into.
No, this is going to push our app into our data repository.
There are going to get up and let's just move back and refresh this page.
So if you refresh it.
You'll see your source code here, as well as the red meat already added with it.
Now we have a repository right here, so let's just move back into ahead of UCLA and search for all
the repositories that we have.
So we're here, we're having all the repositories, so the name of our repository travels, right?
So just search for travelers.
So here we have a repository, just connectivity.
So no one's connected.
Just wait for Clia to pass before deploying and Will automatically applies.
And before we deploy our branch, we need to add a battery pack to it.
So just moving to your settings.
And just scroll down and here have to add a belt back for our React app.
So for this purpose, we will just move.
We very back.
And this is the address of the fact that we're going to copy.
So we'll have to paste this link into our belt back option.
So if you want to search for it manually, do I provided you in the links?
All you have to do is search for a remarkable pack
rat pack edible.
And this will take you to the next go to get educated about with the Link Create reactor and this is
your link which you want to page with you.
So just copy this link.
And move back into your travel list dashboard and click on Add Back.
And paste your link over here and there and just see if changes.
So now you see a problem saying that you are better power configurations will be used when the app is
next deployed.
So now let's just again move back into our deploying.
And now we'll just click on Deploy, everything has been set up.
And I just click on Deploy and it is going to take some time.
And after Nadia, we deployed.
So now that our app has been deployed, let's view Add app, you can see this view button.
Just click on it.
And it will open it up.
OK, so here is a wrap and it has been successfully deployed.
Now anyone from around the world can just access it with this utterly.