So now that we are Arab has been created, so we will move into our territory just CD and directly,
and that is he travels.
And then when the command court with a period and this will open up, are we as court instance now?
The first thing that will do is to clean up an entire Arab component because we will be starting everything
from fresh now will be creating all the tools that it's going to hold, all of our components of our
tour, of our tour app.
The first of them is going to be a dashboard that is our dashboard Thanatos component, then a third
component so that those components is going to map all our data into the total component.
That, in turn, will be displaying all of our data.
So in order to discuss the matter, give it up, so that top level component is up, which is followed
by a dashboard, then the toast, then the third component.