So now we're moving to India after GSX failed, and let's create a boilerplate over there.
So the first thing we will do is call a dashboard component in our app component because app is the
parent component of dashboard component.
And once we do this now, let's import dashboard into our Abdul GSX.
So we'll be importing our dashboard into Abdul G6 six.
And once it's done, we have to define its but.
And that, in this case is the cash to splash dashboard.
OK, Sylvia fomented the cold now let's move into our dashboard component and create the boilerplate
where you just create a boilerplate with authority code snippets.
Now the first thing that we're doing our dashboard is that will be adding certain amount of juice and
code.
So if you want to add this amount, this code, you have to just copy paste the file that I provided
along with this tutorial.
So you'll get this stores, which is a static data, and don't worry, you'll be replacing the API calls.
But for timing, we are just using the static data and now that skarlatos component and parcel these
objects and part of the object of two.
So that's important to add component import tool from field slash to.
OK, so we have imported our autos company now will very passing data via props and those equals to
dos and don'ts that go on subject.
It's the area of objects that we have.
Oh, I have no hit safe and let's move into our tour company then.