And import react from the Act module.
And after this, we'll create a concert tour.
So this is again, another function.
And it should be equal to no written statement and will create an article with the class name single
too, and as they'll be reflecting a data only title for the United.
And so it is the ideal but app that title is the name of the place service.
The definition of the place was, as you may see, that.
Let me just check here for the error as a player for that particular place.
Will give image source of material that we are getting from our data usage data.
And let's just close this with our name of Typekit.
And regulate Porter and inside this what I should have inside the sport, I will just keep up inside
of what I will be having first death of tour information and really at last name off to info and actual
bag of hell.
Just this tag is going to be a.
Name of the place that we're going to visit.
So let's just name it came of trip.
So the.
So the consecutive element of style that we have to place in it, and then again, we will be having
an edge for class name of the race.
This is the price of that particular tool and it will be adding, let's just for now give it a stagnant
value of nine seven zero dollars.
And next we were having a paragraph element.
So this paragraph element is the information of the two that we are going to vote on, and the conjugative
element is that they are getting from a dashboard component.
Now you have actually configured most of the tour two component.
Now there's going to be another button class that a user can click to remove that particular face on
the UI.
For example, if someone wants to remove a trip to Big Bend, he might remove it.
If someone wants to remove a trip to Stonehenge, you might remove it.
But for now, it is going to be a stagnant button.
It is not going to do anything, but later on will be adding functionality to it, as you can even see
the properties not used in it, so they will be removed using only property in remove function.
And let's explore the further to it up now.
Hit save and let's take a look at that.
OK, so it.