I app, as it is now, is neither looking great nor beautiful.
Then, after all, it is just pure a.
So in a world representation for this to stand out, we are supposed to add some testosterone so that
it can look at least beautiful and presentable.
So for that purpose, let's move back into our index thesis, and the first step is to clear all the
cases that has been preloaded.
And now be targeting the main main element.
So you might recall that this man is off dashboard, which was holding our tools component.
So it was all from a dashboard of.
So in the function dashboard, we see a day of class name two of men now that's targeted and we're at
a rate of 90 viewport and give it a maximum of 620 pixels and a margin of five in order to hit, save
and see what has happened in our app.
OK, so it has deviated from left as it is right now, I'm going to give it a margin of error to identify
with and or.
OK, no.
Then again, taking the title.
So you might recall the struggles of those component, which was holding it was holding out heading
outdoors.
So outdoors is a child of death with that last name title.
So if we're targeting your title element, then you would expect telling us into a margin, burn them
off for them.
And then we'll just hit save and again, Europe.
OK, so it has been centered, but as you might see, that energy is still non-uniform.
Some of them are quite big, some of them it's quite small.
So we need to refactor this code a bit more.
So that again will be targeting underlined last year at a rate of extreme height of.
0.2 firearm and background of edges are two of 78 by the 60 percent and a margin left of auto and a
margin rate of auto again.
No, just hits it and lets you grab a game.
So, OK, so we can see the vomiting that we didn't just know.
Now, let's head back to our two's company, and you might recall this is the underlying element that
we just have targeted now.
No more into enthusiasts and we target this time the single tour element of our tour component.
So in the tour, we have a single tour.
And it is the article element of class name single to.
So basically, we're targeting the card of our doors inaugurated, give it a October of hashtag Bar-Lev.
So basically this is right, but with a slightly different view and a border radius of zero point of
item and a margin of 210.
And zero and a boxer, a shadow of zero five pixels, 15 pixels and RGV of zero zero and zero point
one.
Now, I'll give it that transition off on 0.3 seconds linear.
No hits ever in Europe.
OK, so begins your car component, you might see that slightly raised a portion of our guides as well
as the information.
OK, so it seems it seems to be working now.
That's move back and add a single to so that whenever we have about Overgaard.
It gives up.
A box set of 05 fixes and 15 pixels with IGB of zero zero zero point one.
Then hit save.
And now will be targeting.
Single to imagine if you want them to be uniform, a uniform and size, because these are non-uniform
at present.
OK, so just go back and we'll give it away to 100 percent a height of 2010 and object of it cover.
You want it to cover it, but stop it.
I traded a zero one two five Adam and border bottom left radius of zero 0.01.
Then just hit save now you can see all of our images out of similar shapes and sizes.
So this is good because this gives a uniformity to our app.
Now go back and read together to add info.
So basically, this time we are targeting the information that is being displayed in our tool component.
So as you might see the tour info which contains the title as well as a price.
And the subheading.
OK, let's go back to an index thesis.
And.
Give it a display of flex justified content of space between.
And it's a.
So, OK, it has been implemented now.
The spaces between our title, as well as Price now adding items to the center.
Margin bottom of.
Let's give it.
1.5 Jim and two it and four of each food.
Margin bottom.
Zero.
So if he gets it in Europe now.
OK, so it been implemented now, let's go back and our index to assess and give it a single.
We are targeting single button element, and you're the background of transparent, we do not own the
background that if our button's background and as well give it.
So we see that default button background has been removed now.
And now let's just go back and give it a color transparent, we want to absolutely remove every default
characteristics of the button.
No text transition of Capralos transform capitals.
And we want every, every word in it to be capitalized.
And now we're not interested.
OK, then again, will you read the color of itself to a fire 78 percent and 60 percent?
And if one size of wonder and of course, a pointer.
And betting that 0.5mm.
Now, if we just Europe.
OK, so Britain has a different color now.
And it is looking good.
Now, let's head back to our ambassadors and give tours price.
The pricing of our two of you might remember that in autos component, we have a tool price class or
the class name to price know your decoder.
It is said to have 78 and 60 percent.
Background color features a dual 500 percent and 96 percent.
And let's say and let's fill it up again, so we are hearing about it now as well as a price has a different
color.
Now getting into it first with your departing of 0.5 Iranian, 0.5 Iran, because they wanted to slightly
shift away from the borders and a border radius, or zero point of evidence.
OK, so it's working now.
No, Tiger does include for that and give it a padding of 0.7 one podium and do them.
And the single to.
OK, let's just remove it and give it single to delete button.
Basically, you might remember that this button is not doing anything but just for it's just for this
plant will be adding dynamic start later on.
So if you were a display of it and imagine, but we want it to be in the center, not away from the
day of even the center.
So let's just say that it went to zero in auto.
So there's really a central element.
It's a case of our investor button has been internal or no margin of wondering and the color of three
sixty six, 360, 67 percent, forty 44 percent and letter spacing of zero point two hundred and a background
color of transparent.
It's very transparent, it's safe.
OK, so here you have a spacing.
And adverts now, crystal clear.
OK, so each and every element has been placed successfully now below the border of a solid and natural
killer of 30, 60, 67 percent and 44 percent, and a padding of 0.5 firearm and 0.5 them and a border
radius of zero point about him.
No effective and we are up again, so it is looking slightly better, a lot better if we compare to
the previous version of Arab.
Then again, we'll just.
If you are up, there are certain pre batting and margins, added Ed Ed Components Web Browser, So
we will be removing all those by the following code.
We want to we are targeting the entire record and we want after and before.
The margin should be zero.
As well as the padding should be zero and a boxer you should be worried about.
And we'll give it a foreign body font family of Apple system background color of Excel two and zero.
36 percent 96 percent A color of SSL to a nine, 61 and 16 percent and a line height of 1.5 percent
with a font size of zero point eight seven five.
So if it just hits, if not, we'll see on a slightly different color.
And all those patterns and margins have disappeared now, so we have successfully added scissors to
add up.
Though they're not invest.
Button is not working now.
We'll be adding functionalities to it in the coming tutorial.
So we have successfully added all the capabilities and functions to it up.