He will import react from the Act module, then will create a clone stores, which is out of function.
Then a return call will return a statement.
And this has got a section.
And inside that section, there's going to be a day of class name title.
And in this title will have an extra element of our doors
and a day of class classroom underline.
Now we'll go out of this div and create another level of class name list.
And inside this list will be having.
So let's just restructure the objects that we are receiving and that the stores will be mapping that
there to the object so that each and every element of it can be displayed on a UI.
We're just mapping those that map and it will take about two document and then return.
And call our tour component, and the function of the store component is to display each and every object
specifically.
So now we have our third component right in front of us.
And using the spread of radar will be just transmitting all the data that we have and as you might be
aware about the height and structure of our app.
So let's just first important component from the address period slash tour, and it'll be sending our
data to the tour.
And now let's just export before the value tools component.
After this, after this will be heading to our third component to configure it.
So now let's just move to a two component.